Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
=Twin Fates=
=مصيران توأمان=
=Episode 21= (I Will Die For You)
=الحلقة 21= (سأموت من أجلك)
♪In a world of sorrows, every encounter is fleeting♪
♪في عالم من الأحزان، كل لقاء عابر♪
(When the sacrificial Day of Xihe comes,)
(وعندما يأتي يوم التضحية Xihe)
(I'll fulfill my promise and save your clan members.)
(سأنفذ وعدي وأنقذ أعضاء عشيرتك.)
♪Life is short but slumber is long on Penglai Island♪
♪الحياة قصيرة ولكن النوم طويل في جزيرة بنغلاي♪
(If our separation is inevitable,)
(إذا كان انفصالنا أمرا لا مفر منه)
(may these last days)
(أتمنى أن تكون هذه الأيام الأخيرة)
(be worthwhile.)
(يكون جديرًا بالاهتمام.)
♪All I ever wish for is an old friend's return♪
♪كل ما أتمناه هو عودة صديق قديم♪
♪Majestic as a soaring dragon, veiling the sun with drifting clouds♪
♪مهيب مثل التنين المرتفع، يحجب الشمس بالغيوم المنجرفة♪
Don't go.
لا تذهب.
♪Graceful as a flying swan goose, breaking through snow and peril♪
♪رشيقة مثل أوزة البجعة الطائرة، تخترق الثلوج والخطر♪
Did... Did I wake you up?
هل... هل أيقظتك؟
You've been gazing at me.
لقد كنت تحدق بي.
What are you looking at?
ماذا تنظر اليه؟
♪Twenty years forsaken, I lived the life of an outlaw♪
♪بعد عشرين عامًا من الإهمال، عشت حياة خارج عن القانون♪
I...
أنا...
I was wondering
كنت أتساءل
when you'd wake up from your nap,
عندما تستيقظ من قيلولتك،
Scarlet Flame Divine Hog.
الخنزير الإلهي ذو اللهب القرمزي.
♪Bit by bit, reality shatters my only hope♪
♪شيئًا فشيئًا، الواقع يحطم أملي الوحيد♪
I was kidding.
لقد كنت أمزح.
Don't be mad.
لا تغضب.
♪Layer by layer, cold blades roll up the light I once glimpsed in secret♪
♪طبقة بعد طبقة، شفرات باردة تتدحرج نحو الضوء الذي لمحته ذات مرة سرًا♪
Are you angry?
هل أنت غاضب؟
♪Letters have long since yellowed♪
♪لقد اصفرت الحروف منذ زمن طويل♪
Well,
حسنًا،
you're messing with me again, huh?
أنت تتلاعب معي مرة أخرى، أليس كذلك؟
♪Even the old yard is covered with frost♪
♪حتى الفناء القديم مغطى بالصقيع♪
♪Bit by bit, reality shatters my only hope♪
♪شيئًا فشيئًا، الواقع يحطم أملي الوحيد♪
♪Layer by layer, cold blades roll up the light I once glimpsed in secret♪
♪طبقة بعد طبقة، شفرات باردة تتدحرج نحو الضوء الذي لمحته ذات مرة سرًا♪
Stop right there!
توقف هنا!
♪Letters have long since yellowed♪
♪لقد اصفرت الحروف منذ زمن طويل♪
♪Leaving only two lonely lines♪
♪ترك خطين وحيدين فقط♪
♪Even the old yard is covered with frost♪
♪حتى الفناء القديم مغطى بالصقيع♪
♪Pair after pair, swallows draw my envious gaze♪
♪زوجًا بعد زوج، تجذب السنونو نظرتي الحسود♪
Not... Not this trick again.
لا... ليس هذه الخدعة مرة أخرى.
I'm killing two birds
أنا أقتل عصفورين
with one stone here.
بحجر واحد هنا.
♪While you rest beneath the earth♪
♪بينما تستريح تحت الأرض♪
♪My love lingers in this frosty world♪
♪حبي يبقى في هذا العالم البارد♪
♪How are you now?♪
♪كيف حالك الآن؟♪
Your heart is pounding.
قلبك ينبض بقوة.
So is yours.
وهكذا هو حالك.
That's because my heart is close to you.
لأن قلبي قريب منك.
♪How are you now?♪
♪كيف حالك الآن؟♪
Have you thought it through?
هل فكرت في الأمر جيدا؟
Tomorrow's the Day of Xihe.
غدا هو يوم Xihe.
I will fulfill our promise
سأفي بوعدنا
and remove the seal off the Scarlet Flame Clan.
وإزالة الختم عن عشيرة اللهب القرمزي.
The Land of Scarlet Flame
أرض اللهب القرمزي
shall be as vital as before.
سوف تكون حيوية كما كانت من قبل.
♪The autumn wind stirs ripples on the lake♪
♪رياح الخريف تثير تموجات على البحيرة♪
♪I never saw the promised sea of blossoms♪
♪لم أرى أبدًا بحر الأزهار الموعود♪
Yet there's no perfection
ولكن لا يوجد الكمال
in this world.
في هذا العالم.
There's a price to everything.
لكل شيء ثمن.
♪What we lived was never written, only carried in the heart♪
♪ما عشناه لم يُكتب أبدًا، بل حمله القلب فقط♪
♪I sigh, for all beings are bound by fate♪
♪أتنهد، لأن جميع الكائنات مرتبطة بالقدر♪
When it's all over,
عندما ينتهي كل شيء،
you must check out this prosperous world
يجب عليك التحقق من هذا العالم المزدهر
and the vast galaxy
والمجرة الشاسعة
on my behalf.
بالنيابة عني.
Experience every sunrise and sunset,
استمتع بكل شروق وغروب للشمس،
every dawn and dusk.
كل فجر وغسق.
No.
لا.
You must see them yourself.
يجب عليك أن تراهم بنفسك.
♪The swaying bamboo unsettles a quiet heart♪
♪الخيزران المتمايل يزعزع قلبًا هادئًا♪
♪Words by the western window hold me captive through the night♪
♪الكلمات عند النافذة الغربية تأسرني طوال الليل♪
♪It's a fleeting dream that feel all too real♪
♪إنه حلم عابر يبدو حقيقيًا للغاية♪
♪That I follow without question♪
♪أنني أتبعها دون أي سؤال♪
♪As I question the swift passing of spring, the quiet rain soaks us both♪
♪ بينما أتساءل عن مرور الربيع السريع، يغمرنا المطر الهادئ ♪
♪Time flows gently, yet I cannot bear to see it pass♪
♪يمر الوقت بهدوء، ولكنني لا أستطيع أن أتحمل مروره♪
♪Sorrow etches itself into every word♪
♪الحزن ينقش نفسه في كل كلمة♪
We'll be fine.
سوف نكون بخير.
♪Helpless before a love too deep♪
♪عاجز أمام حب عميق جدًا♪
♪It leaves my body marked with scars♪
♪يترك جسدي مليئا بالندوب♪
♪Love and hate, all too brief, the years make us strangers♪
♪الحب والكراهية، كلاهما قصيران جدًا، السنوات تجعلنا غرباء♪
♪The swaying bamboo unsettles a quiet heart♪
♪الخيزران المتمايل يزعزع قلبًا هادئًا♪
♪Words by the western window hold me captive through the night♪
♪الكلمات عند النافذة الغربية تأسرني طوال الليل♪
♪It's a fleeting dream that feel all too real♪
♪إنه حلم عابر يبدو حقيقيًا للغاية♪
♪That I follow without question♪
♪أنني أتبعها دون أي سؤال♪
♪As I question the swift passing of spring, the quiet rain soaks us both♪
♪ بينما أتساءل عن مرور الربيع السريع، يغمرنا المطر الهادئ ♪
♪Time flows gently, yet I cannot bear to see it pass♪
♪يمر الوقت بهدوء، ولكنني لا أستطيع أن أتحمل مروره♪
♪Sorrow etches itself into every word♪
♪الحزن ينقش نفسه في كل كلمة♪
♪Like a dream too brief, leaving only the memory of someone I once knew♪
♪مثل حلم قصير جدًا، لا يترك سوى ذكرى شخص عرفته ذات يوم♪
Chi Yu, what's the matter with you?
تشي يو، ما الأمر معك؟
(Hand the Xuanzhu Jade over!)
(قم بتسليم Xuanzhu Jade!)
Mu Lingxue!
مو لينج شيو!
Today is the Day of Xihe,
اليوم هو يوم Xihe
making it the best time to extract the Xuanzhu Jade.
وهذا ما يجعل هذا الوقت هو الأفضل لاستخراج اليشم Xuanzhu.
Stop being arrogant.
توقف عن الغطرسة.
You're just An Sha's puppet.
أنت مجرد دمية في يد آن شا.
You
أنت
have no idea how powerful An Sha is.
ليس لدي أي فكرة عن مدى قوة An Sha.
The Xuanzhu Jade isn't in you?
هل اليشم Xuanzhu ليس بداخلك؟
(Where's my Xuanzhu Jade?)
(أين اليشم Xuanzhu الخاص بي؟)
Speak. Where is it?
تكلم. أين هو؟
Stop it!
اوقفها!
The Xuanzhu Jade is now in me.
اليشم Xuanzhu هو الآن في داخلي.
Come and take it if you can.
تعال وخذها إذا كان بوسعك.
You...
أنت...
You're burning my evil spirit!
أنت تحرق روحي الشريرة!
Your real form
شكلك الحقيقي
and the remnant soul in me
والروح الباقية في داخلي
share
يشارك
the same fate.
نفس المصير
You've been torturing me with your evil spirit.
لقد كنت تعذبني بروحك الشريرة.
Since you want the Xuanzhu Jade so bad,
نظرًا لأنك تريد اليشم Xuanzhu بشدة،
I shall return your favor
سأرد لك معروفك
with its flame!
مع لهبها!
=Twin Fates= =End of Episode 21=
=مصيران توأمان= =نهاية الحلقة 21=
♪In a world of sorrows, every encounter is fleeting♪
♪في عالم من الأحزان، كل لقاء عابر♪
♪Life is short but slumber is long on Penglai Island♪
♪الحياة قصيرة ولكن النوم طويل في جزيرة بنغلاي♪
♪In dreams, mountains and flowers are as beautiful as jade♪
♪في الأحلام، الجبال والزهور جميلة مثل اليشم♪
♪All I ever wish for is an old friend's return♪
♪كل ما أتمناه هو عودة صديق قديم♪
♪Majestic as a soaring dragon, veiling the sun with drifting clouds♪
♪مهيب مثل التنين المرتفع، يحجب الشمس بالغيوم المنجرفة♪
♪Graceful as a flying swan goose, breaking through snow and peril♪
♪رشيقة مثل أوزة البجعة الطائرة، تخترق الثلوج والخطر♪
♪Twenty years forsaken, I lived the life of an outlaw♪
♪بعد عشرين عامًا من الإهمال، عشت حياة خارج عن القانون♪
♪On the Ximo River, who was left behind?♪
♪على نهر شيمو، من بقي خلفه؟♪
♪Bit by bit, reality shatters my only hope♪
♪شيئًا فشيئًا، الواقع يحطم أملي الوحيد♪
♪Layer by layer, cold blades roll up the light I once glimpsed in secret♪
♪طبقة بعد طبقة، شفرات باردة تتدحرج نحو الضوء الذي لمحته ذات مرة سرًا♪
♪Letters have long since yellowed♪
♪لقد اصفرت الحروف منذ زمن طويل♪
♪Leaving only two lonely lines♪
♪ترك خطين وحيدين فقط♪
♪Even the old yard is covered with frost♪
♪حتى الفناء القديم مغطى بالصقيع♪
♪Pair after pair, swallows draw my envious gaze♪
♪زوجًا بعد زوج، تجذب السنونو نظرتي الحسود♪
♪Scene after scene, in dreams I cannot reach♪
♪مشهد بعد مشهد، في الأحلام لا أستطيع الوصول إليه♪
♪While you rest beneath the earth♪
♪بينما تستريح تحت الأرض♪
♪My love lingers in this frosty world♪
♪حبي يبقى في هذا العالم البارد♪
♪How are you now?♪
♪كيف حالك الآن؟♪